[
  {
    "question": "Where is the Niagara Escarpment?",
    "choices": [
      "Ontario",
      "Quebec",
      "Montana",
      "Lake Erie"
    ],
    "answer": "Ontario"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is Frasier Valley?",
    "choices": [
      "Western Chile",
      "Southern Italy",
      "British Columbia",
      "Ohio River Valley"
    ],
    "answer": "British Columbia"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who makes Clos St. Hune?",
    "choices": [
      "Hugel",
      "Trimbach",
      "Deiss",
      "Leroy"
    ],
    "answer": "Trimbach"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the premier cru of Clos St. Jacques?",
    "choices": [
      "Chablis",
      "Morey St. Denis",
      "Gevery Chambertin",
      "Mosel Valley"
    ],
    "answer": "Gevery Chambertin"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is Morgon?",
    "choices": [
      "Provence",
      "Languedoc",
      "Beaujolais",
      "Bordeaux"
    ],
    "answer": "Beaujolais"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is Juliénas?",
    "choices": [
      "Chablis",
      "Little Rock",
      "Beaujolais",
      "Macon"
    ],
    "answer": "Beaujolais"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is Chiroubles?",
    "choices": [
      "Germany",
      "Beaujolais",
      "Savoie",
      "Bordeaux"
    ],
    "answer": "Beaujolais"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is Fleurie?",
    "choices": [
      "Bordeaux",
      "Savoie",
      "Beaujolais",
      "Champagne"
    ],
    "answer": "Beaujolais"
  },
  {
    "question": "Alte Reben on a German wine label means what?",
    "choices": [
      "Vines over 20 years old",
      "Vines over 50 years old",
      "New vines",
      "Old vines"
    ],
    "answer": "Old vines"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the soils of Santorini?",
    "choices": [
      "Alluvial",
      "Volcanic",
      "Granite",
      "Gneiss"
    ],
    "answer": "Volcanic"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which country commands the highest price per bottle on average in the world?",
    "choices": [
      "USA",
      "Portugal",
      "Australia",
      "New Zealand"
    ],
    "answer": "New Zealand"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who makes the wine \"g-max\"?",
    "choices": [
      "Doctor Bernkastler",
      "Weingut Keller",
      "Dr. Loosen",
      "Weingut Wittmann"
    ],
    "answer": "Weingut Keller"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the grape of Chinon blanc?",
    "choices": [
      "Cabernet Sauvignon",
      "Pinot Noir",
      "Sauvignon Blanc",
      "Chenin Blanc"
    ],
    "answer": "Chenin Blanc"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Hungary's largest region?",
    "choices": [
      "Kunság",
      "Sopron",
      "Bern",
      "Mosel"
    ],
    "answer": "Kunság"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the southern most AOP of the Northern Rhône Valley?",
    "choices": [
      "Hermitage",
      "Southern Plains",
      "St. Joseph",
      "St-Péray"
    ],
    "answer": "St-Péray"
  },
  {
    "question": "What grape is used for Klevener de Heiligenstein?",
    "choices": [
      "Reisling",
      "Sauvignon Blanc",
      "Pinot Noir",
      "Savagnin rose"
    ],
    "answer": "Savagnin rose"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is Bodegas Chacra located?",
    "choices": [
      "Argentina",
      "Chile",
      "Italy",
      "Spain"
    ],
    "answer": "Argentina"
  },
  {
    "question": "The alluvial plain of what river is found in Emilia Romagna?",
    "choices": [
      "New Gusto",
      "Nile",
      "Po",
      "Mosel"
    ],
    "answer": "Po"
  },
  {
    "question": "What growth in the Bordeaux classification is Château Palmer?",
    "choices": [
      "2nd",
      "Cru Bourgeois",
      "3rd",
      "None"
    ],
    "answer": "3rd"
  },
  {
    "question": "What growth in the Bordeaux classification is Château Pontet-Canet?",
    "choices": [
      "3rd",
      "5th",
      "2nd",
      "6th"
    ],
    "answer": "5th"
  },
  {
    "question": "What growth in the Bordeaux classification is Château Kirwan?",
    "choices": [
      "4th",
      "Super Second",
      "3rd",
      "Cru Bourgeois"
    ],
    "answer": "3rd"
  },
  {
    "question": "What growth in the Bordeaux classification is Château Lascombes?",
    "choices": [
      "3rd",
      "8th",
      "5th",
      "2nd"
    ],
    "answer": "2nd"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is Château Bouscaut located?",
    "choices": [
      "Provence",
      "Jura",
      "Burgundy",
      "Graves"
    ],
    "answer": "Graves"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is Domaine de Chevalier located?",
    "choices": [
      "Chinon, France",
      "Graves, France",
      "SW France",
      "Cadiz, Spain"
    ],
    "answer": "Graves, France"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is Château Pape-Clément located?",
    "choices": [
      "Burgundy",
      "Graves",
      "Loire Valley",
      "Pomerol"
    ],
    "answer": "Graves"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is château Sainte-Roseline located?",
    "choices": [
      "Savoie",
      "Provence",
      "Bordeaux",
      "Mosel"
    ],
    "answer": "Provence"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the Cote de Lechet located?",
    "choices": [
      "Provence",
      "Bordeaux",
      "Champagne",
      "Chablis"
    ],
    "answer": "Chablis"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is Vaucopins located?",
    "choices": [
      "Chablis",
      "Champagne",
      "Levant",
      "South Africa"
    ],
    "answer": "Chablis"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the min. ammount of Sangiovese for Vino Nobile di Montepulciano DOCG?",
    "choices": [
      "20 percent",
      "70 percent",
      "50 percent",
      "none"
    ],
    "answer": "70 percent"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is Lake Balanton?",
    "choices": [
      "Romania",
      "Northern Chile",
      "Eastern Italy",
      "West Hungary"
    ],
    "answer": "West Hungary"
  },
  {
    "question": "Sea breezes called Meltemi are found where?",
    "choices": [
      "Spain",
      "Chile",
      "Portugal",
      "Greece"
    ],
    "answer": "Greece"
  },
  {
    "question": "What river runs through Rioja?",
    "choices": [
      "Ebro",
      "Ombrone",
      "Rhone",
      "Tiber"
    ],
    "answer": "Ebro"
  },
  {
    "question": "What river runs through Valtelina?",
    "choices": [
      "Loess",
      "Hudson",
      "Po",
      "Adda"
    ],
    "answer": "Adda"
  },
  {
    "question": "What river runs through Cahors?",
    "choices": [
      "Lot",
      "Algarve",
      "Porto",
      "Vienne"
    ],
    "answer": "Lot"
  },
  {
    "question": "What river runs through Vouvray?",
    "choices": [
      "Brenne",
      "Hudson",
      "Riesling",
      "Po"
    ],
    "answer": "Brenne"
  },
  {
    "question": "What river runs through Barbaresco?",
    "choices": [
      "Adda",
      "Tanaro",
      "Russian",
      "Italian"
    ],
    "answer": "Tanaro"
  },
  {
    "question": "What river runs through Tokaj?",
    "choices": [
      "Po",
      "Carpathian",
      "Bodrog",
      "Nebbiolo"
    ],
    "answer": "Bodrog"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the Guadalete River?",
    "choices": [
      "Jerez",
      "Madrid",
      "Italy",
      "Barcelona"
    ],
    "answer": "Jerez"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the Piave River?",
    "choices": [
      "Portugal",
      "Veneto",
      "Umbria",
      "Liguria"
    ],
    "answer": "Veneto"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is Lake Neuchatel?",
    "choices": [
      "France",
      "Germany",
      "Chile",
      "Switzerland"
    ],
    "answer": "Switzerland"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is Lake Balaton?",
    "choices": [
      "Portugal",
      "Italy",
      "Chile",
      "Hungary"
    ],
    "answer": "Hungary"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is Lake Trasimeno?",
    "choices": [
      "France",
      "Portugal",
      "Spain",
      "Italy"
    ],
    "answer": "Italy"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where are the Dentelles Mountians located?",
    "choices": [
      "Northern Chile",
      "Southern France",
      "Western Portugal",
      "Spain"
    ],
    "answer": "Southern France"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the Mt. Lofty Ranges located?",
    "choices": [
      "McLaren Vale, Australia",
      "Porto, Portugal",
      "Santiago, Chile",
      "Southern France"
    ],
    "answer": "McLaren Vale, Australia"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the the Great Dividing Range located?",
    "choices": [
      "NSW, Australia",
      "Mosel, Germany",
      "Western Italy",
      "Chile"
    ],
    "answer": "NSW, Australia"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the Finger Lakes AVA?",
    "choices": [
      "Virginia",
      "Ohio",
      "Vermont",
      "New York"
    ],
    "answer": "New York"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which parent company produces Bond?",
    "choices": [
      "Cakebread",
      "Rodney Strong",
      "Mateus",
      "Harlan"
    ],
    "answer": "Harlan"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which grape is used in the white wines of Soave?",
    "choices": [
      "Pinot Gris",
      "Riesling",
      "Garganega",
      "Chardonnay"
    ],
    "answer": "Garganega"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which white grape is most associated with the Rueda region of Spain?",
    "choices": [
      "Cabernet Sauvignon",
      "Syrah",
      "Verdejo",
      "Merlot"
    ],
    "answer": "Verdejo"
  },
  {
    "question": "What mountain range protects Alsace?",
    "choices": [
      "Dentelles",
      "Vosges",
      "Alps",
      "Massif Central"
    ],
    "answer": "Vosges"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is Colmar?",
    "choices": [
      "Bordeaux",
      "Burgundy",
      "Alsace",
      "Provence"
    ],
    "answer": "Alsace"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is grés de Vosges?",
    "choices": [
      "Weather pattern in Bordeaux",
      "Soil in Alsace",
      "Mountain range in Jura",
      "Lake in Savoie"
    ],
    "answer": "Soil in Alsace"
  },
  {
    "question": "What grape may be included in the bottle if an Alsatian wine says Pinot Blanc?",
    "choices": [
      "Auxerrois",
      "Aligote",
      "Rousette",
      "Melon Blanc"
    ],
    "answer": "Auxerrois"
  },
  {
    "question": "Tokay d’Alsace was once a common name for what grape?",
    "choices": [
      "Pinot Gris",
      "Aligote",
      "Rousette",
      "Melon Blanc"
    ],
    "answer": "Pinot Gris"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is Kanzlerberg?",
    "choices": [
      "Alsace",
      "Lorraine",
      "Provence",
      "Loire Valley"
    ],
    "answer": "Alsace"
  },
  {
    "question": "Cotes de toul resides in which larger growing AOP?",
    "choices": [
      "Jura",
      "Lorraine",
      "Provence",
      "Loire Valley"
    ],
    "answer": "Lorraine"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which is not a main grape of the Jura?",
    "choices": [
      "Poulsard",
      "Trousseau",
      "Pinot Noir",
      "Aligote"
    ],
    "answer": "Aligote"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which region may not produce vin de paille?",
    "choices": [
      "Arbois",
      "L'Etoile",
      "Macvin du Jura",
      "Côtes du Jura"
    ],
    "answer": "Macvin du Jura"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is Lake Bourget?",
    "choices": [
      "Bordeaux",
      "Savoie",
      "Alsace",
      "Moselle"
    ],
    "answer": "Savoie"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where are the Brokenback Mountains?",
    "choices": [
      "Albany",
      "Hunter",
      "Gisbourne",
      "Margaret River"
    ],
    "answer": "Hunter"
  },
  {
    "question": "Tyrrell’s Vat 1 is made in which appellation?",
    "choices": [
      "Hunter Valley",
      "Mornington Peninsula",
      "Canberra District",
      "Barossa Valley"
    ],
    "answer": "Hunter Valley"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which region is shared between New South Wales and the Australian Capital Territory?",
    "choices": [
      "Mornington Peninsula",
      "Canberra District",
      "Barossa Valley",
      "Hunter Valley"
    ],
    "answer": "Canberra District"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which region does the Port Phillip Bay influence?",
    "choices": [
      "Mornington Peninsula",
      "Canberra District",
      "Orange",
      "Southern Highlands"
    ],
    "answer": "Mornington Peninsula"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which AVA is not in San Luis Obispo County?",
    "choices": [
      "Paso Robles",
      "Arroyo Grande",
      "North Yuba",
      "Edna Valley"
    ],
    "answer": "North Yuba"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which area is not in Ontario?",
    "choices": [
      "Niagara Peninsula",
      "Lake Erie North Shore",
      "Pelee Island",
      "Frasier Valley"
    ],
    "answer": "Frasier Valley"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which is a synonym Chardonnay in Switzerland?",
    "choices": [
      "Morillon",
      "Melon Blanc",
      "Romorantin",
      "Moscatel"
    ],
    "answer": "Morillon"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is Château Chalon AOP?",
    "choices": [
      "Jura",
      "Champagne",
      "Burgundy",
      "Bordeaux"
    ],
    "answer": "Jura"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which region ripens first?",
    "choices": [
      "Alsace",
      "Burgundy",
      "Bordeaux",
      "Jura"
    ],
    "answer": "Alsace"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which area is in British Columbia?",
    "choices": [
      "Niagara Peninsula",
      "Lake Erie North Shore",
      "Pelee Island",
      "Frasier Valley"
    ],
    "answer": "Frasier Valley"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which region is closest in proximaty to the Cognac region?",
    "choices": [
      "Bordeaux",
      "Burgundy",
      "Alsace",
      "Provence"
    ],
    "answer": "Bordeaux"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the main grape of the Cornas region?",
    "choices": [
      "Grenache",
      "Syrah",
      "Mourvedre",
      "Cinsault"
    ],
    "answer": "Syrah"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the main grape of the Côte-Rôtie region?",
    "choices": [
      "Grenache",
      "Syrah",
      "Mourvedre",
      "Cinsault"
    ],
    "answer": "Syrah"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is Palette?",
    "choices": [
      "Rhône Valley",
      "Provence",
      "Champagne",
      "Loire Valley"
    ],
    "answer": "Provence"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is St. Bris AOP?",
    "choices": [
      "Alsace",
      "Burgundy",
      "Bordeaux",
      "Jura"
    ],
    "answer": "Burgundy"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is Passe-Tout-Grains produced?",
    "choices": [
      "Alsace",
      "Burgundy",
      "Bordeaux",
      "Jura"
    ],
    "answer": "Burgundy"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is Barsac AOP?",
    "choices": [
      "Alsace",
      "Burgundy",
      "Bordeaux",
      "Jura"
    ],
    "answer": "Bordeaux"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the minimum ABV % for Pomerol wines?",
    "choices": [
      "10",
      "11",
      "12",
      "13"
    ],
    "answer": "11"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is Ajaccio AOP?",
    "choices": [
      "Alsace",
      "Corsica",
      "Bordeaux",
      "Jura"
    ],
    "answer": "Corsica"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the Monticello AVA?",
    "choices": [
      "Oregon",
      "Virginia",
      "New York",
      "Ohio"
    ],
    "answer": "Virginia"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the Central Coast AVA?",
    "choices": [
      "Oregon",
      "California",
      "New York",
      "Washington State"
    ],
    "answer": "California"
  },
  {
    "question": "What grape is most likely growing in Ribbon Ridge?",
    "choices": [
      "Pinot Noir",
      "Cabernet Franc",
      "Merlot",
      "Grenache"
    ],
    "answer": "Pinot Noir"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is Bergerac AOP?",
    "choices": [
      "Southern Rhône Valley",
      "Provence",
      "SW France",
      "Loire Valley"
    ],
    "answer": "SW France"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is Monbazillac?",
    "choices": [
      "Rhône Valley",
      "Western Provence",
      "SW France",
      "Loire Valley"
    ],
    "answer": "SW France"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is Cour-Cheverny?",
    "choices": [
      "Rhône Valley",
      "Western Provence",
      "SW France",
      "Loire Valley"
    ],
    "answer": "Loire Valley"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is Chateau Grillet?",
    "choices": [
      "Rhône Valley",
      "Western Provence",
      "SW France",
      "Loire Valley"
    ],
    "answer": "Rhône Valley"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is Greco di Tufo DOCG?",
    "choices": [
      "Tuscany",
      "Abruzzo",
      "Campania",
      "Piedmont"
    ],
    "answer": "Campania"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is Taurasi DOCG?",
    "choices": [
      "Tuscany",
      "Abruzzo",
      "Campania",
      "Piedmont"
    ],
    "answer": "Campania"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where would you find the Dolcetto grape growing?",
    "choices": [
      "Tuscany",
      "Abruzzo",
      "Campania",
      "Piedmont"
    ],
    "answer": "Piedmont"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where would you find the Fiano grape growing?",
    "choices": [
      "Tuscany",
      "Abruzzo",
      "Campania",
      "Piedmont"
    ],
    "answer": "Campania"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the Geisenheim Wine Institute?",
    "choices": [
      "France",
      "Germany",
      "Austria",
      "Hungary"
    ],
    "answer": "Germany"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the Goldtröpfchen vineyard?",
    "choices": [
      "Rheingau",
      "Mosel",
      "Rheinhessen",
      "Nahe"
    ],
    "answer": "Mosel"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the Ürziger Würzgarten vineyard?",
    "choices": [
      "Rheingau",
      "Mosel",
      "Rheinhessen",
      "Nahe"
    ],
    "answer": "Mosel"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which region does the Eifel Mountains influence?",
    "choices": [
      "Rheingau",
      "Mosel",
      "Ahr",
      "Nahe"
    ],
    "answer": "Ahr"
  },
  {
    "question": "Spätburgunder is a synonym for which grape in Germany?",
    "choices": [
      "Grenache",
      "Syrah",
      "Pinot Noir",
      "Cinsault"
    ],
    "answer": "Pinot Noir"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the bocksbeutel bottle utilized?",
    "choices": [
      "Rheingau",
      "Baden",
      "Ahr",
      "Franken"
    ],
    "answer": "Franken"
  },
  {
    "question": "What does trocken indicate on a German wine label?",
    "choices": [
      "Sweet",
      "Dry",
      "Sparkling",
      "Aged"
    ],
    "answer": "Dry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where would you find the designation Districtus Austriae Controllatus (DAC)?",
    "choices": [
      "France",
      "Germany",
      "Austria",
      "Hungary"
    ],
    "answer": "Austria"
  },
  {
    "question": "What city would you find Wiener Gemischter Satz being produced?",
    "choices": [
      "Budapest",
      "Venice",
      "Vienna",
      "Berlin"
    ],
    "answer": "Vienna"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which is not a subregion of the Douro Valley?",
    "choices": [
      "Baixo Corgo",
      "Cima Corgo",
      "Douro Superior",
      "Minho Superior"
    ],
    "answer": "Minho Superior"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which region is guarded by a \"rain shadow\" effect of the local mountains?",
    "choices": [
      "Bordeaux",
      "Alsace",
      "Champagne",
      "Provence"
    ],
    "answer": "Alsace"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the Auckland wine region?",
    "choices": [
      "Australia",
      "New Zealand",
      "Argentina",
      "Chile"
    ],
    "answer": "New Zealand"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the Mornington Peninsula wine region?",
    "choices": [
      "Australia",
      "New Zealand",
      "Argentina",
      "Chile"
    ],
    "answer": "Australia"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the Torrontés grape most likley grown?",
    "choices": [
      "Spain",
      "New Zealand",
      "Argentina",
      "Chile"
    ],
    "answer": "Argentina"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the Shoalhaven Coast wine region?",
    "choices": [
      "Australia",
      "New Zealand",
      "Argentina",
      "Chile"
    ],
    "answer": "Australia"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the Kumeu wine region?",
    "choices": [
      "Australia",
      "New Zealand",
      "Argentina",
      "USA"
    ],
    "answer": "New Zealand"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the Gisbourne wine region?",
    "choices": [
      "Australia",
      "New Zealand",
      "Argentina",
      "Chile"
    ],
    "answer": "Australia"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the Bannockburn wine region?",
    "choices": [
      "Australia",
      "New Zealand",
      "Argentina",
      "Chile"
    ],
    "answer": "New Zealand"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the Limestone Coast wine region?",
    "choices": [
      "Australia",
      "New Zealand",
      "Argentina",
      "USA"
    ],
    "answer": "Australia"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the Yarra Valley wine region?",
    "choices": [
      "Australia",
      "New Zealand",
      "Argentina",
      "Chile"
    ],
    "answer": "Australia"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the Luján de Cuyo wine region?",
    "choices": [
      "Spain",
      "New Zealand",
      "Argentina",
      "Chile"
    ],
    "answer": "Argentina"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where are the Criolla Grande and Cereza grapes most prevalent?",
    "choices": [
      "Australia",
      "New Zealand",
      "Argentina",
      "Chile"
    ],
    "answer": "Argentina"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is Viñedo Chadwick produced?",
    "choices": [
      "Uruguay",
      "Spain",
      "Argentina",
      "Chile"
    ],
    "answer": "Chile"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who produces Clos Apalta?",
    "choices": [
      "Montes",
      "Torres",
      "Casa Lapostolle",
      "Concha Y Toro"
    ],
    "answer": "Casa Lapostolle"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who produces Don Melchor?",
    "choices": [
      "Montes",
      "Torres",
      "Casa Lapostolle",
      "Concha Y Toro"
    ],
    "answer": "Concha Y Toro"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which grape is found in Chile more than it is found in Argentina?",
    "choices": [
      "Merlot",
      "Carmenère",
      "Syrah",
      "Pinot Noir"
    ],
    "answer": "Carmenère"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the Uco Valley?",
    "choices": [
      "San Juan",
      "Mendoza",
      "Maipo",
      "Santiago"
    ],
    "answer": "Mendoza"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is Retsina produced?",
    "choices": [
      "Greece",
      "Hungary",
      "Romania",
      "Bulgaria"
    ],
    "answer": "Greece"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the Paros wine region?",
    "choices": [
      "Greece",
      "Hungary",
      "Romania",
      "Bulgaria"
    ],
    "answer": "Greece"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where are the islands of Lemnos and Rhodes?",
    "choices": [
      "Greece",
      "Hungary",
      "Romania",
      "Bulgaria"
    ],
    "answer": "Greece"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which mountain range impacts the Tokaj regoin?",
    "choices": [
      "Alps",
      "Carpathian",
      "Dentelles",
      "Dolomite"
    ],
    "answer": "Carpathian"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is Egri Bikavér produced?",
    "choices": [
      "Greece",
      "Hungary",
      "Romania",
      "Bulgaria"
    ],
    "answer": "Hungary"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the Great Southern wine region?",
    "choices": [
      "Australia",
      "New Zealand",
      "Argentina",
      "USA"
    ],
    "answer": "Australia"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the Gaillac wine region?",
    "choices": [
      "Provence",
      "Languedoc",
      "Rousillon",
      "SW France"
    ],
    "answer": "SW France"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the Madiran wine region?",
    "choices": [
      "Provence",
      "Languedoc",
      "Rousillon",
      "SW France"
    ],
    "answer": "SW France"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the Monbazillac wine region?",
    "choices": [
      "Provence",
      "Languedoc",
      "Rousillon",
      "SW France"
    ],
    "answer": "SW France"
  },
  {
    "question": "What style of wine is produced in Monbazillac?",
    "choices": [
      "Dry Red",
      "Dry White",
      "Sweet White",
      "All of these"
    ],
    "answer": "Sweet White"
  },
  {
    "question": "What style of wine is produced in Cahors?",
    "choices": [
      "Dry Red",
      "Dry White",
      "Sweet White",
      "All of these"
    ],
    "answer": "Dry Red"
  },
  {
    "question": "What style of wine is produced in Carmignano?",
    "choices": [
      "Dry Red",
      "Dry White",
      "Sweet White",
      "All of these"
    ],
    "answer": "Dry Red"
  },
  {
    "question": "What style of wine is produced in Bardolino Superiore?",
    "choices": [
      "Dry Red",
      "Dry White",
      "Sweet White",
      "All of these"
    ],
    "answer": "Dry Red"
  },
  {
    "question": "What style of wine is produced in Soave Superiore?",
    "choices": [
      "Dry Red",
      "Dry White",
      "Sweet White",
      "All of these"
    ],
    "answer": "Dry White"
  },
  {
    "question": "What style of wine is produced in Nobile di Montepulciano?",
    "choices": [
      "Dry Red",
      "Dry White",
      "Sweet White",
      "All of these"
    ],
    "answer": "Dry Red"
  },
  {
    "question": "What style of wine is produced in Cerasuolo di Vittoria DOCG?",
    "choices": [
      "Dry Red",
      "Dry White",
      "Sweet White",
      "All of these"
    ],
    "answer": "Dry Red"
  },
  {
    "question": "What style of wine is produced in Valtellina Superiore?",
    "choices": [
      "Dry Red",
      "Dry White",
      "Sweet White",
      "All of these"
    ],
    "answer": "Dry Red"
  },
  {
    "question": "What style of wine is produced in Cònero Riserva DOCG?",
    "choices": [
      "Dry Red",
      "Dry White",
      "Sweet White",
      "All of these"
    ],
    "answer": "Dry Red"
  },
  {
    "question": "What style of wine is produced in Arbois?",
    "choices": [
      "Dry Red",
      "Dry White",
      "Sweet White",
      "All of these"
    ],
    "answer": "All of these"
  },
  {
    "question": "What style of wine is produced in l'Etoile?",
    "choices": [
      "Vin Jaune",
      "Dry White",
      "Sweet White",
      "All of these"
    ],
    "answer": "All of these"
  },
  {
    "question": "What style of wine is produced in Cornas?",
    "choices": [
      "Dry Red",
      "Dry White",
      "Sweet White",
      "All of these"
    ],
    "answer": "Dry Red"
  },
  {
    "question": "What style of wine is produced in Château-Grillet?",
    "choices": [
      "Dry Red",
      "Dry White",
      "Sweet White",
      "All of these"
    ],
    "answer": "Dry White"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the maximum residual sugar % found in Crémant de Die?",
    "choices": [
      "12 g/l",
      "15 g/l",
      "21 g/l",
      "33 g/l"
    ],
    "answer": "15 g/l"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Edelfäule the Germanic term for?",
    "choices": [
      "single vineyard",
      "noble rot",
      "cooperative producer",
      "hand harvest"
    ],
    "answer": "noble rot"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which grape is most associated with Chinon?",
    "choices": [
      "Sauvignon Blanc",
      "Chenin Blanc",
      "Chardonnay",
      "Pinot Gris"
    ],
    "answer": "Chenin Blanc"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which grape is most associated with Cote Chalonais?",
    "choices": [
      "Sauvignon Blanc",
      "Chenin Blanc",
      "Chardonnay",
      "Pinot Gris"
    ],
    "answer": "Chardonnay"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which grape is most associated with Graves?",
    "choices": [
      "Sauvignon Blanc",
      "Chenin Blanc",
      "Chardonnay",
      "Pinot Gris"
    ],
    "answer": "Sauvignon Blanc"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which country has the most Cabernet Sauvignon under vine?",
    "choices": [
      "France",
      "USA",
      "Australia",
      "Spain"
    ],
    "answer": "USA"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which country has the least Cabernet Sauvignon under vine?",
    "choices": [
      "France",
      "USA",
      "Australia",
      "Spain"
    ],
    "answer": "Australia"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which grape is most associated with Sauternes?",
    "choices": [
      "Sauvignon Blanc",
      "Chenin Blanc",
      "Chardonnay",
      "Pinot Gris"
    ],
    "answer": "Sauvignon Blanc"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the Penedès wine region?",
    "choices": [
      "France",
      "Spain",
      "Italy",
      "Portugal"
    ],
    "answer": "Spain"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the Jumilla  wine region?",
    "choices": [
      "France",
      "Spain",
      "Italy",
      "Portugal"
    ],
    "answer": "Spain"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the Montilla-Moriles wine region?",
    "choices": [
      "France",
      "Spain",
      "Italy",
      "Portugal"
    ],
    "answer": "Spain"
  },
  {
    "question": "What style of wine is produced in Rioja?",
    "choices": [
      "Dry white",
      "Dry red",
      "Sparkling wine",
      "All of these"
    ],
    "answer": "All of these"
  },
  {
    "question": "What style of wine is produced in Rías Baixas?",
    "choices": [
      "Dry white",
      "Dry red",
      "Sparkling wine",
      "All of these"
    ],
    "answer": "All of these"
  },
  {
    "question": "What style of wine is produced in Rueda?",
    "choices": [
      "Dry white",
      "Dry red",
      "Sparkling wine",
      "All of these"
    ],
    "answer": "All of these"
  },
  {
    "question": "What style of wine is produced in Valdeorras?",
    "choices": [
      "Dry white",
      "Dry red",
      "Sparkling wine",
      "All of these"
    ],
    "answer": "All of these"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the Algarve wine region?",
    "choices": [
      "France",
      "Spain",
      "Italy",
      "Portugal"
    ],
    "answer": "Portugal"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the Vinho Verde wine region?",
    "choices": [
      "France",
      "Spain",
      "Italy",
      "Portugal"
    ],
    "answer": "Portugal"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the Dão wine region?",
    "choices": [
      "France",
      "Spain",
      "Italy",
      "Portugal"
    ],
    "answer": "Portugal"
  },
  {
    "question": "What style of wine is produced in Vinho Verde?",
    "choices": [
      "Dry white",
      "Dry red",
      "Sparkling wine",
      "All of these"
    ],
    "answer": "All of these"
  },
  {
    "question": "What style of wine is produced in Douro DOP?",
    "choices": [
      "Dry white",
      "Dry red",
      "Sparkling wine",
      "All of these"
    ],
    "answer": "All of these"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the Bekaa Valley wine region?",
    "choices": [
      "Lebanon",
      "Spain",
      "Italy",
      "Portugal"
    ],
    "answer": "Lebanon"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the Galilee wine region?",
    "choices": [
      "Lebanon",
      "Spain",
      "Italy",
      "Israel"
    ],
    "answer": "Israel"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is Commandaria wine produced?",
    "choices": [
      "Lebanon",
      "Spain",
      "Cyprus",
      "Greece"
    ],
    "answer": "Cyprus"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which grape is most associated with Uruguay?",
    "choices": [
      "Sauvignon Blanc",
      "Malbec",
      "Chardonnay",
      "Tannat"
    ],
    "answer": "Tannat"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which grape is known as Gamay Blanc in the Jura?",
    "choices": [
      "Chardonnay",
      "Sauvignon Blanc",
      "Merlot",
      "Cabernet Franc"
    ],
    "answer": "Chardonnay"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which grape is known as Morillon in the Austria?",
    "choices": [
      "Chardonnay",
      "Sauvignon Blanc",
      "Merlot",
      "Cabernet Franc"
    ],
    "answer": "Chardonnay"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which grape is known as Steen in the South Africa?",
    "choices": [
      "Chardonnay",
      "Sauvignon Blanc",
      "Merlot",
      "Chenin Blanc"
    ],
    "answer": "Chenin Blanc"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the The Rocks of Milton-Freewater wine region?",
    "choices": [
      "Australia",
      "UK",
      "New Zealand",
      "USA"
    ],
    "answer": "USA"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where are the Santa Ynez Mountains?",
    "choices": [
      "California",
      "NY",
      "Oregon",
      "Washington State"
    ],
    "answer": "California"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where are the Mayacamas Mountains?",
    "choices": [
      "California",
      "NY",
      "Oregon",
      "Washington State"
    ],
    "answer": "California"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where are the North Coast Range Mountains?",
    "choices": [
      "California",
      "NY",
      "Oregon",
      "Washington State"
    ],
    "answer": "California"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the Shenandoah Valley?",
    "choices": [
      "California",
      "NY",
      "Virginia",
      "Washington State"
    ],
    "answer": "Virginia"
  },
  {
    "question": "If a wine from Australia has the grape variety on the label, what percentage of that grape must be in the bottle?",
    "choices": [
      "80%",
      "85%",
      "95%",
      "100%"
    ],
    "answer": "85%"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the most planted grape in Australia?",
    "choices": [
      "Merlot",
      "Shiraz",
      "Malbec",
      "Grenache"
    ],
    "answer": "Shiraz"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the Royal Slope AVA?",
    "choices": [
      "Oregon",
      "California",
      "New York",
      "Washington State"
    ],
    "answer": "Washington State"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is Lillooet GI?",
    "choices": [
      "Canada",
      "Australia",
      "Mexico",
      "USA"
    ],
    "answer": "Canada"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is Thompson Valley GI?",
    "choices": [
      "Canada",
      "Australia",
      "Mexico",
      "USA"
    ],
    "answer": "Canada"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the Wahluke Slope AVA?",
    "choices": [
      "Oregon",
      "California",
      "New York",
      "Washington State"
    ],
    "answer": "Washington State"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the Lewis-Clarke AVA?",
    "choices": [
      "Oregon",
      "Idaho",
      "New York",
      "Washington State"
    ],
    "answer": "Idaho"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the Puget Sound AVA?",
    "choices": [
      "Oregon",
      "California",
      "New York",
      "Washington State"
    ],
    "answer": "Washington State"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which grape is most associated with Eden Valley?",
    "choices": [
      "Merlot",
      "Shiraz",
      "Malbec",
      "Grenache"
    ],
    "answer": "Shiraz"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which grape is most associated with Coonawara?",
    "choices": [
      "Merlot",
      "Shiraz",
      "Malbec",
      "Cabernet Sauvignon"
    ],
    "answer": "Cabernet Sauvignon"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which grape is most associated with McLaren Vale?",
    "choices": [
      "Merlot",
      "Shiraz",
      "Malbec",
      "Grenache"
    ],
    "answer": "Shiraz"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is Toro?",
    "choices": [
      "France",
      "Spain",
      "Portugal",
      "Italy"
    ],
    "answer": "Spain"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is Bierzo?",
    "choices": [
      "France",
      "Spain",
      "Portugal",
      "Italy"
    ],
    "answer": "Spain"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is Valdeorras?",
    "choices": [
      "France",
      "Spain",
      "Portugal",
      "Italy"
    ],
    "answer": "Spain"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is Arinzano from?",
    "choices": [
      "France",
      "Spain",
      "Portugal",
      "Italy"
    ],
    "answer": "Spain"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is Vinho Verde produced?",
    "choices": [
      "France",
      "Spain",
      "Portugal",
      "Italy"
    ],
    "answer": "Portugal"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the DOP of Colares?",
    "choices": [
      "France",
      "Spain",
      "Portugal",
      "Italy"
    ],
    "answer": "Portugal"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is Bairrada?",
    "choices": [
      "France",
      "Spain",
      "Portugal",
      "Italy"
    ],
    "answer": "Portugal"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is Moscatel do Douro produced?",
    "choices": [
      "France",
      "Spain",
      "Portugal",
      "Italy"
    ],
    "answer": "Portugal"
  }
]